[
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 8? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "200.96",
      "options": [
        "200.96",
        "202.46",
        "203.96",
        "199.46"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 16? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "803.84",
      "options": [
        "802.34",
        "805.34",
        "806.84",
        "803.84"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 14? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "615.44",
      "options": [
        "615.44",
        "613.94",
        "618.44",
        "616.94"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 34? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "3629.84",
      "options": [
        "3631.34",
        "3628.34",
        "3632.84",
        "3629.84"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 34? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "3629.84",
      "options": [
        "3628.34",
        "3629.84",
        "3632.84",
        "3631.34"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 20? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "1256.0",
      "options": [
        "1257.5",
        "1254.5",
        "1259.0",
        "1256.0"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 35? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "3846.5",
      "options": [
        "3846.5",
        "3845.0",
        "3848.0",
        "3849.5"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 11? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "379.94",
      "options": [
        "382.94",
        "378.44",
        "379.94",
        "381.44"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 15? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "706.5",
      "options": [
        "706.5",
        "705.0",
        "708.0",
        "709.5"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 31? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "3017.54",
      "options": [
        "3017.54",
        "3016.04",
        "3020.54",
        "3019.04"
      ]
    }
]